Guide to the Spyros P. Skouras Papers M0509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4: Twentieth Century Fox
  - Production - Films
    - Little Shepard Of Kingdom Come (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - The Long Hot Summer (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - The Longest Day - Advertising, Publicity & Exploitation (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - The Longest Day - Budget And Contractual (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - The Longest Day - Casting And Dubbing (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - The Longest Day - DFZ - SPS Personal Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - The Longest Day - Music (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - The Longest Day - Premiere (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - The Longest Day - Prints And Recordings (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - The Longest Day - Production Progress (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - The Longest Day - Release And Distribution (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - The Longest Day - Reviews And Comments (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - The Longest Day - Script And Story (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - The Longest Day - Souvenir Journal (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - The Longest Day - Special Personnel (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Love Is A Many Splendored Thing (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - The Magus (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - A Man Called Peter (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Man In The Grey Flannel Suit (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - The Man Who Never. Was (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Marines Let's Go (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - The Mark (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Masters Of The Congo Jungle (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - The Millionaires (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Mr. Hobbs Takes A Vacation (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Misty (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Nice Little Bank That Should Be Robbed (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Nine Hours To Rama (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - No Down Payment (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - North To Alaska (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Oasis (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Oklahoma (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Only For Love (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - On The Threshold Of Space (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Oscar Wilde (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Patton (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Peyton Place (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Prince Of Players (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - The Queen's Guard (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - The Racers (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - The Rains Of Ranchipur (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Return To Peyton Place (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - The Robe (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - The Roots Of Heaven (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Sanctuary (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - The Sand Pebbles (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Satan Never Sleeps (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Seven Thieves (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Seven Women From Hell (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Seven Year Itch (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Sink The Bismark (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Snow White And The Three Stooges (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Soldier Of Fortune (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Some Came Running (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Something's Got To Give (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Sons And Lovers (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - The Sound Of Music (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - South Pacific (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Star! (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - State Fair (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - The Story Of Ruth (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - The Stripper (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - The Sun Also Rises - General (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - The Sun Also Rises - Cast (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Take Her, She's Mine (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ten North Frederick (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Tender Is The Night - General, 1959 - 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Tender Is The Night - General, 1961 - 1962 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Tender Is The Night - Academy Award Eligibility (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Tender Is The Night - Premieres, Previews And Release (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - There's No Business Like Show Business (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Those Magnificent Men In Their Flying Machines (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - The 300 Spartans - General (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - The 300 Spartans - Budget and Financial (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - The 300 Spartans - Casting And Billing. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - The 300 Spartans - Insurance (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - The 300 Spartans - Music And Re-Recording (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - The 300 Spartans - Script And Story (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - The 300 Spartans - Spyros D. Skouras, Greece (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Tora! Tora! Tora! (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - The Trapp Family (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Two Teddy Bears (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Violent Saturday (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Virgin Queen (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The Visit (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Van Ryan's Express (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - The Wayward Bus (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter? (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The World Of Marilyn Monroe (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - The Young Lions (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Zorba The Greek (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Requests For Film For Benefits
    - Request for film benefits (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Films Made
    - Kennedy, John F. (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Royal Greek, Wedding (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Production in Greece
    - Production in Greece (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Projected Films
    - General (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - "Man With The Worry Beads" (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - "Rupel" (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Rossellini's Acts Of The Apostles (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Rejected Properties
    - Books: General, 1956 - 1962 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Books: General, 1963 - 1971 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Films: General, 1957 - 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Films: Dreamland Of Desire (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Films: Rejected By TCF But Released By Others (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: General (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Battle Of Leyte Gulf (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Dr. Dooley Story (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Greek Tourist Film (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: In This Sign (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Justine (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: The King Must Die (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: The Miracle Of Guadelupe (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: The Odyssey: A Modern Sequel (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Saladin (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Films Proposed But Not Made: Short Cut (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Films Made But Not Released: Tiger In.The Tea (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Films Made But Not Released: Unknown India (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General, 1954 - 1960 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General, 1961 Jan-March (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General, 1961 April-June (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General 1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: General 1963-69 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: De Brochgrave, Arnaud (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Scripts, Stories, &.Screenplays: Properties Written Off, 1944 - 1960 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Production - Advertising
    - General (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Production - Agents
    - Feldman, Charles (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - General Artists Corp. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - William Morris Agency (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Production - Censorship
    - General (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Legion Of Decency (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Production - Directors
    - Kazen, Elia (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Cukor, George (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Dassin, Jules (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Production Distribution
    - Rank Organization - 16mm Films (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Rejected (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Production - Distribution Deals
    - General (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Rank Organization. Canada (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Rank Organization - Goumont - British (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Production Exploitation
    - Production - Exploitation (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Production - Heads Of Studio
    - Adler, Buddy, Jan~-Sept 1956 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Adler, Buddy, Oct - Dec 1956 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Buddy, Jan-Sept 1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Adler, Buddy, Oct-Dec 1957 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Adler, Buddy, Jan-May 1958 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Adler, Buddy, June-Dec 1958 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Adler, Buddy, Jan-July 1959 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Adler, Buddy, Aug-Dec 1959 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Adler, Buddy, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Adler, Buddy: Personal (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Goldstein, Bob, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Goldstein, Bob, Jan 1961-4-3-61 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Goldstein, Bob, 4-4-61-Oct 1962 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Levathes, Peter: Personal (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Levathes, Peter, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Levathes, Peter, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Zanuck, D.F.: Personal SPS-DFZ (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Zanuck, D.F.: Personal (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1949 - 1954 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1955 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1956 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1957 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1958 - 1959 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Zanuck, D.F., 1960 - 1967 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Zanuck, Richard (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Production - Industrial Films & TV Commercials
    - Production - Industrial Films & TV Commercials (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Production - Legal
    - Legal matters (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Production - Studio Managers
    - Schreiber, Lew (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Production - Music Rights
    - Music Rights (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Production - Producers
    - Allen, Irwin (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Alperson, Edward (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - BHE Products Ltd. (Lord Brabourne) (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - De Sica, Vittorio (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Engel, Sam (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Feldman, Charles (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Figaro Prods. (Joseph Mankiewicz) (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Galatea Prods. (Lionello Santi) (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - General (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Graetz, Paul (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Johnson, Nunnally (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Lippert, Robert, 1956 - June 1961 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Lippert, Robert, July 1961 - 1963 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Litvak, Anatole (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Mccarey, Leo (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Panoramic Prods. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Powell, Michael (Emeric Prods.) (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Powell, Richard (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Radnitz, Robert (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Ratoff, Gregory (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Robson, Mark (Red Lion Prods.) (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Rossen, Robert (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Selznick, David 0. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Seven Arts Prods. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Shergari Prods. (F.H. Ricketson) (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Stevens, George (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Sumar Prods. (Andre Hakim) (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Titanus Films V(Godfreddo Lombardo) (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Wald, Jerry (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Wanger, Walter (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Production Sales (Domestic)
    - General (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Advertising (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - All-Branch Letters From Sps (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Branch Operations (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Canada & Canada/USA (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Comments From The Field (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Conn, Rob. Exec. Asst. In Charge Of Domestic Distribution (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Conventions (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Norris, Glen - Sales Manager (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Trailer Film - The Big Show (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Reports on Films to DFZ, 1962 - 1967 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Zanuck, Darryl Francis
  - Production Sales (Foreign)
    - General (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Australia (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Brazil (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Egypt (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - France (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Germany (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Greece, 1960 - 1961 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Greece, 1962 -1 967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - India (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Israel (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Italy (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Japan (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Mexico (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - New Zealand (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Spain (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - United Kingdom (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Branch operations (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Conventions (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Field reports on new products (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Production Sales - Promotions
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - General 1 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Congratulations: Misc. Foreign (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Congratulations: Relatives (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Congratulations: Relatives: VIPs (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Congratulations: Trade, Press, & Organ. (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Dinner, 4/2/62 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - 20th Anniversary Campaign - Special Drive (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - 15th Anniversary Campaign 1957 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Production Schedules
    - Potential (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Progress (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Release (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Production Talent
    - Artists: General, 1954-60 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Artists: General, 1961-67 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Artists: Bergman, Ingrid (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Artists: Greco, Juliette (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Artists: Hudson, Rock (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Artists: Kaye, Danny (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Artists: Lollobrigida, Gina (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Artists: Loren, Sophia (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Artists: Monroe, Marilyn (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Artists: Presley, Elvis (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Creative - Other General (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Public Comments re: Artists (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Public Comments re: request for talent appearances (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Studio Training School (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Music - General (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Real Estate
    - General (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Herrscher, Edmund, 1956 - 1957 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Herrscher, Edmund, Jan-Jun 1958 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Herrscher, Edmund, Jul-Dec 1958 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Herrscher, Edmund, 1959 - 1961 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Villa Douchka - Cap d' Antibes (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Oil properties (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Subsidiaries
    - De Lux Laboratories - general (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Movietone News: general (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Movietone News: British (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Movietone News: Financial (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Movietone News: Government subsidy (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Movietone News: U.P. Hearst / MGM deals (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Movietone News: Short subjects division (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 20th Century Fox: general (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - 20th Century Fox: applications (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - 20th Century Fox: Cain, Ted (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - 20th Century Fox: Csida, Joe (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - 20th Century Fox: merger possibilities (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - 20th Century Fox: Onorati and Del Guercio (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - 20th Century Fox: Reports to Daryl F. Zanuck (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - 20th Century Fox: Sound track albums (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Television Station KMSP, 1958-62 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Television Station KMSP, Jan-Jun 1963 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Television Station KMSP, Jul-Dec 1963 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Television Station KMSP, 1964-68 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Television Station KMSP: General Offers (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Television Station KMSP: Goodwill Stations (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Television Station KMSP: Sale Of Station - Polaris (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Television Station KMSP: Screen Gems (Col.) (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Technical Processes
    - Todd A. O. - General (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Todd A. O., 1954-61 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Todd A. O., 1962-7 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Cinemascope: 1st Anniversary Congratulations (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Cinemascope: Comments General (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Cinemascope: Cinemascope 55 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Cinemascope: Demonstration Reel (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Cinemascope: General (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Cinemascope: Installations, Lenses, Etc. (Domestic) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Cinemascope: Installations, Lenses, Etc. (Foreign) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Cinemascope: Short Subjects (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Cinemascope: Stereophonic Sounds (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Eidophor: General (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Eidophor: Ciba & Phillips Corp. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Eidophor: General Electric Corp. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Eidophor: Theater Network T.V. Corp. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - 3-D: Professor Cuvier (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Television
    - Foreign: General (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Foreign: Australia (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Foreign: Greece (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Foreign: Greece ABC Deal (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Foreign: South Africa (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Foreign: United Arab Emirates (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Foreign: United Kingdom (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - TCF Production, 1955-61 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - TCF Production, 1962-68 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Agents - William Morris (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Administrative & Financial (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Personnel (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Series: General (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Series: Hong Kong Series 4: Twentieth Century Fox, Television (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - 20th Century Fox-General Electric Hour (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Legal - Network Production Anti-Trust Suit (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Organizations- T.V. Program Export Assn. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: General (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: AT & T (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: CaTv (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: Etobicoke (Can) Experiment (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: Hartford Experiment (Zenith) (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: Home Entertainment Co., Inc. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Pay & Theatrical T.V.: Mitchell, Xenophon (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Feature Film Sales To T.V.: Television - General (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Feature Film Sales To T.V.: General (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Feature Film Sales To T.V.: National Telefilm Associates (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Financial - Various Reports, Domestic & Foreign (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Independent Prod. - Seven Arts Prods. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Theatre Holdings (Overseas)
    - Australia: Drive-In Theatres (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Australia: General, 1954-60 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Australia: Hoyts, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Australia: Hoyts, 1960-64 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Australia: Hoyts, 1962-68 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Australia: U.A.-Fox Merged Distribution Operation (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - England: Gaumont-British (Rank Org.), 1954-61 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - England: Reports From Mr. Duval & Mr. Kent, 1960-61 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Egypt - General (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - New Zealand - General (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Proposed acquisitions or construction of theatres (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - South Africa: General (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - South Africa: Fox Theatres South Africa Pty. Ltd. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - South Africa: Goldstein, Leon (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - South Africa: Insurance (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - South Africa: Kinemas (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - South Africa: Rank Org. deal (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - South Africa: Rhodesian political situation (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - South Africa: South African political situation (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - South Africa: Schlesinger, John (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1958 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1960 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - South Africa: Administration - All operations, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - South Africa: African Consolidated Films, 1956 - 1958 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - South Africa: African Consolidated Films, 1959 - 1963 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - South Africa: Cinerama Deal (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - South Africa: Drive-In Theatre (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - South Africa: MGM Deal (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - South Africa: Paramount Deal (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - South Africa: United Artists Deal (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - South Africa: Warner Bros. / Allied Artists / Columbia / Universal Deals (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - South Africa: African Film Productsion (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Investments And Projects
  - Investments - Projects
    - General (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Aluminum Production (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Automobiles, Greece (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Bottling Plant Greece (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Brazilian Warehouse & Silo (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Canning (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Coca-Cola Greece (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Egypt: Purchase Of T.V. Sets For UAR Govt. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Egypt: Purchase Of Air Conditioning For T.V. Bldg In Egypt (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Egyptian Finance Project (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Ethiopian (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Films: Damaskinos & Michaelidis (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Films: Finos (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Films: Hughes, Howard (Various) (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Films: "The Late Liz" (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Films: "The Tree" (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Films: Sullivan, Michael (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Greek Tourism (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - IOS (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Pepsi-Cola Greece 1 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Pepsi-Cola Greece 2 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Oil: General (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Oil: Greek Refineries, Vol. I (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Oil: Greek Refineries, Vol. II (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Oil: Greek Refineries, Vol. III (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Oil: Greek Refineries, Vol. IV (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Ore General (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Possible Mergers: General (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Possible Mergers: Cumberland Farms (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Possible Mergers: Flying Tigers (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Possible Mergers: Litton Industries (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Possible Mergers: UATC/Commonwealth United (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Possible Mergers: Wetzel, Stuart (Associates) (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Greece (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Instant Housing' Corp. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Lockheed Aircraft Service (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Saudi Arabia (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Turkey (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Pre-Fabricated Houses: Turkey & Greece (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Race Track (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Real Estate: S S Florida (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Real Estate: Greece (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Real Estate: RIC (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Shipping: Cuban Naval Co. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Shipping: Tanker Construction (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Shipping: U.S. Coat Shipments To Germany (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Skourohori Project (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Steel Greece (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Suez Canal Project (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Swine Breeding (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - UAR General (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Xelopan Greece
    - Xe1opan Greece (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Xelopan Industries, S.A. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Agenda: Conference On Agreements (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Agreement Between JCP-Pappas Co. - SPS-Superwood & AID (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Agreement Between TCP-Pappas Co. - SPS-Superwood & Eximbank (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Credit Agreement: Xelopan-Aid (Box 56, Folder 7)